

Le Thi Binh

Date of Birth 17/01/1999 Gender Female

Phone 0393 367 160

Email lebinh99pt@gmail.com

Address 333/40 Xuan Dinh, Bac Tu Liem, Ha Noi

PROFILE

I have graduated in English at Phuong Dong university. I am looking forward to finding job related to English in reputed company, having challenge to gain more experience and knowledge. Impressed Quote "A winner never stops trying" I try my best at all times and I believe that I can complete the mission well.

EDUCATION

09/2017 - Present Student English, Chinese faculty at Phuong Dong university.

Studied at Long Chau Sa high school

09/2014 - 05/2017 Joined district level excellent student contest

(2015 - literature subject)

EXPERIENCE

07/2018 - 6/2019

Work part time in convenience store near university

- Organizing the good on shelves
- To be responsible for cashier
- Reporting for owner
- Cleaning the work area

10/2017 - 05/2018

Work part time job in food restaurants with role of waitress

- Serve food and drinks to customers
- Answer customers' questions about menu items, providing consultation.
- Clean tables and dining areas

PASSIONS

Cooking Reading Traveling